jaaxy.com 2019-07-24

# Jaaxy Privacy Policy

## Jaaxy Privacy Policy

We take your privacy seriously and take measures to provide all users of the Jaaxy platform with a safe and secure environment.  This starts with requiring only basic information to join our service, and the ability to use pseudonyms and usernames.

When this policy mentions “we” or “us,” it refers to the controller of your information under this policy. Your information is controlled by Jaaxy (Sky City & Global Sync Marketing Inc.),  Box 18 2354 Millstream Rd Victoria, BC, Canada V9B 6L2.

You should read this entire policy to learn more about how we handle privacy, data, and how we use any information that you provide.  However, here are a few key points.

  * We require only basic information from you including name, and email to create an account with our service. You may use any information you wish, including pseudonyms if you would like to remain anonymous.

  * Any information entered into the system as a logged in user may be publicly visible or searchable including name, or content like questions, blog posts, training, public profile description, or comments.

  * Any personal information entered into the system can be updated and reviewed at any time from your account [settings page](https://my.jaaxy.com/account/details).  You may change this information at any time, or (as of May 25th, 2018) request to have your account removed entirely, removing any personally identifiable information within our internal systems.

  * When you use Jaaxy, even if you’re just browsing as a guest, we receive some information from you like the type of device you’re using and your IP address. 

## What Our Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how Jaaxy treats personal information that is collected and received, including information related to your use of Jaaxy products and internal services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

## Information Collected

Jaaxy collects personal information when you register, when you use our products or services, or when you visit our pages. When joining Jaaxy you are required to enter a name, and email address.  This basic information is collected so that we can provide you with our services and log you in. Once registered and signed into our services, this information is available to us.

Jaaxy may collect information about your interactions with us, keyword searches, use of the research tools within the platform, or any other area where you can enter and input content to the system.  For example, when performing a keyword search, saving keyword lists, or using the SiteRank system.

We automatically receive and record information in server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Jaaxy.com cookie information, and the page you requested.  The information in server logs is kept for a 60 day period in order to provide us with information to improve services and debug potential technical issues that may arise, protect against fraud, or malicious activity.

We provide control through the account settings to limit the data we collect from you and how we use it, as well as to control things like email communication, name, or email used for logging in.  This information is visible to you within your [account settings](https://my.jaaxy.com/account/details) at anytime.  It is not important to us to know your real identity. If you prefer to be anonymous then you can change your name, username, and email to anything that you like.  Likewise on your public profile, you can choose to enter an image and add a description.  Images and profile descriptions can be removed at any time by visiting your public profile at:

<https://my.jaaxy.com/account/details>

We use your information to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting.  If you have questions about this policy, how we collect or process your personal data, or anything else related to our privacy practices, we would love to hear from you. You can contact us at any time.

## Information Sharing

No personal content entered into Jaaxy is public or immediately visible and searchable by anyone.  Questions, keyword searches, site rank searches, or any other activity within Jaaxy is visible to others.  You may participate within Jaaxy under a pseudonym (alternate name), and if you do not choose to use your real name this is completely fine.  Your email address is not shared publicly.

Your Jaaxy account activity is shared only with our sister company WealthyAffililate.com if you choose to connect your account.  In this case, your keyword lists, keyword searches, and use of Jaaxy will be visible to your Wealthy Affiliate account.  Your email address is shared with WealthyAffiliate.com for the sole purpose of verification if you wish to connect an account to that platform, and only if you explicitly have a Wealthy Affiliate account.  This allows for integration into the WA platform and to give you the same great Jaaxy experience at the click of a button in WA.

We engage service providers to perform functions and provide services to us.  For example, we use a variety of third-party services to help operate our services, such as keyword research, site rank, and to help us understand the use of our services. We may share your private personal data with such service providers subject to obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions. Your payment information is forwarded to payment services providers to process payments; prevent, detect, and investigate fraud or other prohibited activities; facilitate dispute resolution such as chargebacks or refunds; and for other purposes associated with the acceptance of credit and debit cards.

In the event that Jaaxy is merged or acquired by another company, your information may be transferred to that entity.  We will notify you before any information about you is transferred or of any changes to this privacy related to this process.

## Cookies

Jaaxy.com may set and access WealthyAffiliate.com cookies on your computer.  Cookies are used to keep you logged into our platform and to provide our system with the basic information to provide the services you are requesting.  Cookies can be cleared at any time from your internet browser settings.

## Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may make changes to our Privacy Policy in the future, however, the most current version of the policy will govern our processing of your personal data and will always be available at the following URL: <https://www.jaaxy.com/privacy>. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you by an update or email to the email address associated with your Jaaxy account. By continuing to access or use our services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
